A Guide to the Papers of Rear Admiral Walter C. Ansel, 1924-1974
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Documents of the German Military during World War II
  - Naval War Staff (Skl. - Kriegsmarine)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Airforce General Staff, Supreme Naval Group Command West, Naval Command West, and Admiral Commanding France, 31 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 43)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, Naval Command West, and Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 2 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Army General Staff, Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, and Naval Command West, 3 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding France, Supreme Naval Command West, Admiral Commanding the Netherlands, etc, 5 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval departments A(A VI), etc., 6 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval departments A(A VI), etc., 9 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval departments A(A VI), etc., 10 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 6)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Ob.d.M. and the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, 11 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 7)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, 12 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 8)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval departments OAK 16, OAK 9, 13 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 9)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, Naval Command West, Admiral Commanding France, and Supreme Naval Group Command North, 14 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 10)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Commands North and West, 16 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 11)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding the Port of Hamburg, Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 12)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command North, 18 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 13)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 20 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 14)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding France, 21 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 15)
    - 1/Skl. report on the Transport Fleet and its location, 25 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 16)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding France, 3 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 17)
    - 1/Skl. report on the Transportation Fleets strength and location, 4 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 18)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.M., Naval War Staff, Naval Command West, 6 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 19)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.M., Naval War Staff, Naval Command West, 7 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 20)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Commands West and North, and other naval departments, 10 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 21)
    - 1/Skl. report to O.K.W., Chief of the Naval War Staff, and other naval departments on the standing of Sea Lion, 15 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 22)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.W. and the Army General Staff, 17 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 23)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Commands West and North, Admiral Commanding France, Naval Command West, 19 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 24)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval department AMVR, 21 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 25)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Army General Staff, 23 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 26)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.W., 25 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 27)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 29 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 28)
    - 1/Skl. report on the meeting between the Chief of Staff of the Armed Forces High Command and the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, 4 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 29)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Chief of Staff of the Army General Staff and naval department A VI, 5 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 30)
    - 1/Skl. memo to the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, 6 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 31)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding France and the location of transports in various ports, 9 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 32)
    - 1/Skl. memo to the General Staffs of the Army and Airforce, Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding France, and Naval Commander West, 10 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 33)
    - 1/Skl. memo to the Naval Liason to the Army General Staff and naval departments A, M, WA, K, AMA, 12 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 34)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.M., Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding France, and other naval departments, 15 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 35)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding France, 20 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 36)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding France, Naval Command West, and other naval departments, 21 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 37)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding France, Naval Command West, and other naval departments, 22 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 38)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Ob.d.M. and Naval Group Commander West, 25 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 39)
    - 1/Skl. memo to the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding France, Naval Command West,and other naval departments, 29 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 40)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.W., Chief of staff of the Armed Forces, Transport Chief of Ausland, and other naval departments, 30 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 41)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West and Admiral Commanding France, 3 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 42)
    - 1/Skl. memo to both Army and Airforce General Staffs, 7 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 43)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval department A MA, 13 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 44)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.W., and naval departments A, A VI, A Wa, etc., 16 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 45)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval departments MPA, A MA, and A, 19 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 46)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command, Admiral Commanding the Fleet, Naval Command West, Admiral Commanding France, 22 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 47)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Army General Staff, Supreme Naval Group Command West, and Naval Command West, 31 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 48)
    - 1/Skl. report on Sea Lion, 4 Jan. 1941 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 49)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding France, and Naval Command West, 10 Jan. 1941 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 50)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.W., 25 Jan. 1941 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 51)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding France, and other naval departments, 30 Jan. 1941 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 52)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding France, 4 Feb. 1941 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 53)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Army General Staff, Supreme Naval Group Command West, and other naval commands, 15 Feb. 1941 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 54)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding France, 17 Feb. 1941 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 55)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding France, Naval Command Schall-Edmen, 19 Feb. 1941 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 56)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Naval Brance AMA, 28 Feb. 1941 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 57)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.W. and the Army General Staff, 7 Mar. 1941 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 58)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding France, and Naval Command West, 3 Apr. 1941 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 59)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.W., 16 Apr. 1941 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 60)
    - 1/Skl. report on the strength of the Kriegsmarine (no date) (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Supreme Naval Group Command North (Gruppe Nord - Kriegsmarine)
    - Gruppe Nord collection of orders, plans, instructions, and correspondence dealing with Operation Sea Lion, May 1940-Aug. 1941 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Gruppe Nord collection of Naval Command North Sea log book. Part I, 3 Jun. 1940-31 Aug. 1941 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Gruppe Nord collection of Naval Command North Sea log book. Part II, 3 Jun. 1940-31 Aug. 1941 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Gruppe Nord collection of Naval Command North Sea log book. Part III, 3 Jun. 1940-31 Aug. 1941 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Admiral Commanding the Netherlands, Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Gruppe Nord plan by Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command North, General Admiral Cans, 1938 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 29 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Gruppe Nord log book on Sea Lion preparations, Jul-Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Gruppe Nord report to Chief of Staff of the Naval Group North West, 8 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command, 9 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command, 23 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command, 25 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Gruppe Nord log book, Aug-Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command, 10 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command, 11 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command, 14 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff and Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 15 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to the Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 16 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Naval War Staff, 17 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 20 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to the Naval War Staff and other naval departments, 22 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to the Naval War Staff and other naval departments, 24 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to the Naval War Staff, 27 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 29 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 5 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Ob.d.M., 9 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Naval Command West, 10 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Air Force General Staff and Air Fleets Five and Two, 13 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 19 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 20 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Gruppe Nord report on the Admiral Commanding the Netherlands log book, Sept. 1940-Nov. 1941 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Admiral Commanding Coastal Installations, 2 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Gruppe Nord memo to Naval Command Netherlands, 2 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Admiral Commanding Norway memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 10 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Coastal Command of Northern Frozen Land Memo to Command Naval Station of the North Sea, 28 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Gruppe Nord report on the Study of Norway, Sept.-Oct. 1939 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Commander of Security in the Baltic Sea memo to the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, 25 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Supreme Naval Group Command West (Gruppe West - Kriegsmarine)
    - Gruppe West memo to the Naval War Staff, Naval Station North, Coastal Command South West, 19 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Gruppe West memo to Commanding Naval Officer of Holland, 24 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Gruppe West memo to Admiral Commanding France, 16 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Gruppe West memo to O.K.M, 17 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Gruppe West memo to the Naval War Staff, 21 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Gruppe West memos to Admiral Commanding Norway; Naval War Staff; Danau Flottila, 22 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Memos to Gruppe West from FDV; Danau Flottila; Naval War Staff, 23 Jul. 1940; 24 Jul. 1940; 24 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Gruppe West memo to the Naval War Staff and Supreme Naval Group Command; Gruppe West memo to the Naval War Staff, 25 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Gruppe West memo to the Naval War Staff, 26 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Gruppe West memo to Admiral Commanding Norway, Naval Department A, and the Operations Department of the Naval War Staff, 27 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Gruppe West memo to Admiral Commanding the Fleet, 28 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Gruppe West memos to Admiral Commanding France; Naval Port Command Wilhelmshaven, 4 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Memos to Gruppe West from Naval Staff West; Admiral Commanding the Fleet, 5 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Chief of Staff of the Supreme Naval Group Command to the Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 6 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Gruppe West memo to O.K.M., 7 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Gruppe West memo to O.K.M., 8 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Memo to Gruppe West from FDV West; Gruppe West memo to the Naval War Staff, 10 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Gruppe West memo to the Naval War Staff, 11 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Gruppe West memos to Gruppe Nord; O.K.M., 13 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Gruppe West memo to FDM West, 14 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Gruppe West memo to Chief of Staff of the Naval Command West, 15 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Gruppe West memo to Chief of Staff of the Naval Command West, 16 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Gruppe West memo to Chief of Staff of the Naval Command West, 17 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Gruppe West memo to Chief of Staff of the Naval Command West, 18 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Gruppe West memos to Naval Command West; Naval Staff West and other naval departments, 19 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Gruppe West memos to Gruppe Nord; Ob.d.M., 20 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Gruppe West memos to Gruppe Nord; Naval Command West, 21 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Memo to Gruppe West from the Chief of Staff of Gruppe West, 22 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Gruppe West memo to Chief of Staff of Gruppe West, 23 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Gruppe West memos to Naval Department BSO; O.K.M.; Admiral Commanding France, 24 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Gruppe West report number three on Sea Lion; memo to Naval Port Commanders, 25 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Memo to Gruppe West from Naval Command West, 26 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Gruppe West memo to Flag Officer Commanding Minesweepers and Naval Group West, 27 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Gruppe West memo to Gruppe Nord and Naval Command West, 28 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Gruppe West memo to Gruppe Nord, 29 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Memo to Admiral Commanding Gruppe West from Naval Command West, 30 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Memos to Gruppe West from Naval Command West; Skl. from Naval Command West; O.K.M. from Naval Staff West, 1 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Gruppe West memo to Gruppe Nord, and Memo to Naval Staff West from Gruppe West, 2 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Gruppe West memos to Gruppe Nord; Naval War Staff, 3 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Gruppe West memos to Gruppe Nord; Naval War Staff, 4 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Gruppe West memo to Naval Command West, 6 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Memo to Gruppe West from Naval Command West, 6 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Memo to Gruppe West from Naval Command West, 7 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Memo to Gruppe West from Naval Department MI, 8 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Gruppe West memo to all Naval Departments, 9 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Memo to Gruppe West from Naval Command West, 10 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Gruppe West memo to Skl. Naval Command West, and Gruppe West memo to Admiral Commanding France, 13 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Gruppe West memo to Transport Chief, 18 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Gruppe West memo to Skl. and Naval Command West, 19 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Gruppe West memo to Gruppe Nord, 20 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Memo to Gruppe West from the Special Staff, 23 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Gruppe West memo to Gruppe Nord, 27 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Gruppe West memo to English Channel Command, 29 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Gruppe West memo to Naval Group Command West, 5 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Gruppe West memo to Naval Group Command West, 7 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Gruppe West memo to Naval Group Command West, 9 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Gruppe West memo to O.K.M. and Skl, 26 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Gruppe West memo to Naval Group Command West, 3 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Gruppe West memo to Naval Staff West and other military branches, 13 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Gruppe West memo to the Special Staff of the Naval Staff West, 20 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Ocean Headquarters West log book, Aug. 1940-Feb. 1941 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Special Staff of the Naval Group Command West, 22 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Admiral Commanding France (Adm. Frankr. - Kriegsmarine)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Port Command Antwerp, 3 Mar. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Command Netherlands, 11 Mar. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Command of the English Channel, Naval Command of the Netherlands and other naval departments, 13 May. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Station North Sea, Naval Port Command Wilhelmshaven, and other naval port commands, 8 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Gruppe West, 20 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Skl., 22 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Gruppe West, 23 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Gruppe West, 25 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Adm. Frankr. memos to Gruppe West; Chief of Staff of Skl., 27 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Gruppe West, 28 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Adm. Frankr. memos to Gruppe West, and Naval Command West, 29 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Command of the English Channel, Naval Command Northern France, and Gruppe West, 1 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Command of the Netherlands, Naval Command of the English Channel, and Naval Command of Northern France, 2 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Gruppe West, 4 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Command of the Netherlands, 6 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M., 14 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M., 15 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Gruppe West, 16 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Commands of the English Channel, Netherlands, and Western France, 27 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Gruppe West and other naval departments, 29 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M. Gruppe West and Naval Command of the English Channel, 30 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M. and Skl., 1 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M. and Naval Command of the Netherlands 3 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Commands of the Netherlands, English Channel, Northern France, and Naval Port Command Antwerp, 5 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M. and other naval departments, 6 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M. and Naval Command West, 10 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Adm. Frankr. briefing report, 11 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M. and Skl., 12 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M. and Skl., 13 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M. and 1/Skl., 15 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Group Command West, 16 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Gruppe West, 17 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M. and 1/Skl., 18 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Command Stations at Rotterdam, Antwerp, Ostende, Dunkirk, etc..., 19 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M. and Skl., 20 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Command of the English Channel, 22 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Gruppe West, 28 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to O.K.M. and 1/Skl., 30 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Adm. Frankr. report to O.K.M. on Sea Lion, 1 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Command of the English Channel, 3 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Command of the English Channel, 4 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Naval Commands of the English Channel and of Northern France, 10 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Adm. Frankr. memo to Ob.d.M. and Skl., 15 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Adm. Frankr. report to O.K.M. on Sea Lion, 16 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 44)